{
    "subject": "Elisabeth_Ludovika_of_Bavaria",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Frederick_William_IV_of_Prussia",
    "human_readable": "Elisabeth Ludovika of Bavaria is married to Frederick William IV of Prussia.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9885579347610474,
            "question": "Was there a royal marriage between Elisabeth Ludovika of Bavaria and Frederick William IV of Prussia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9793868660926819,
            "question": "Was Elisabeth Ludovika of Bavaria married to a Prussian king?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9775087833404541,
            "question": "Who is Elisabeth Ludovika of Bavaria married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9762636423110962,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Elisabeth Ludovika of Bavaria and Frederick William IV of Prussia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9314340949058533,
            "question": "What was the name of Elisabeth Ludovika of Bavaria's husband?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9312918186187744,
            "question": "Who was Frederick William IV of Prussia married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9301736354827881,
            "question": "To whom did Elisabeth Ludovika of Bavaria wed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8993493318557739,
            "question": "Name a famous figure married to Frederick William IV of Prussia."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7788236737251282,
            "question": "Is Elisabeth Ludovika of Bavaria related to any royal family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6590983271598816,
            "question": "Who held the title of Frederick William IV of Prussia?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Elisabeth Ludovika of Bavaria is married to Frederick William IV of Prussia.",
            "html": "yago_10205_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Elisabeth Ludovika of Bavaria related to any royal family?",
            "html": "yago_10205_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name a famous figure married to Frederick William IV of Prussia.",
            "html": "yago_10205_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To whom did Elisabeth Ludovika of Bavaria wed?",
            "html": "yago_10205_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10205_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10205_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10205_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10205_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10205_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10205_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10205_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10205_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10205_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10205_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the evaluation:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. Elisabeth Ludovika of Bavaria and Frederick William IV of Prussia are mentioned as being married in several documents, including file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_10205/re-ranker-msmarco/61.txt and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_10205/re-ranker-msmarco/76.txt."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement that Elisabeth Ludovika of Bavaria was married to Frederick William IV of Prussia. This can be seen from several sources, including direct statements and details about their marriage in 1823."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}